var questions = [
  {
    "question": 'What band released the song "Wild Horses?',
    "option1": "AC/DC",
    "option2": "Guns N' Roses",
    "option3": "Metallica",
    "option4": "Aerosmith",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What breed was Lassie?",
    "option1": "Labrador Retriever",
    "option2": "Beagle",
    "option3": "Collie",
    "option4": "German Shepherd",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What city does the family in Family Guy live in?",
    "option1": "Quahog",
    "option2": "Smallville",
    "option3": "Gotham",
    "option4": "Cloud City",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the Little Mermaids tail?",
    "option1": "Red",
    "option2": "Green",
    "option3": "Gold",
    "option4": "Purple",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Chewbacca?",
    "option1": "Clone",
    "option2": "Jedi",
    "option3": "Human",
    "option4": "Wookie",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mario Bros daytime job?",
    "option1": "Dentist",
    "option2": "Accountant",
    "option3": "Plumber",
    "option4": "Cashier",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the princess in Mario Bros?",
    "option1": "Peach",
    "option2": "Plumb",
    "option3": "Apple",
    "option4": "Orange",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the real name of the American supersoldier, Captain America?",
    "option1": "Luigi",
    "option2": "Clark Kent",
    "option3": "John Jones",
    "option4": "Steve Rogers",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": 'What year did "Thriller" come out?',
    "option1": "1980",
    "option2": "1985",
    "option3": "1982",
    "option4": "1988",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": 'What is a muggle"?',
    "option1": "A non magic person",
    "option2": "A chewable candy",
    "option3": "A type of beer",
    "option4": "A dog breed",
    "answer": "1"
  },
];
